krebsonsecurity.com 2010-05-08

# This policy outlines the personal information handling practices on krebsonsecurity.com. If you give us personal information, we treat it according to this policy, and we use your personal information only in the ways specified when it was collected. We do not otherwise share it.

This policy outlines the personal information handling practices on krebsonsecurity.com.
If you give us personal information, we treat it according to this policy, and we use your
personal information only in the ways specified when it was collected. We do not
otherwise share it.
Types and uses of personal information
In order to post comments and help moderate comments on this Web site, you must first
create an account with a username and password. That information is used to provide you
with access to your profile and comments. The registration system also requires that you
provide a valid email address to confirm your account. Separately, when you email
krebsonsecurity.com, we retain your address and correspondence, which maybe used to
raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
We share aggregated demographic information about our reader base with our third-party
advertising partner [see "Third-party Advertisers"], including browser information and
traffic statistics. We do not link this data to individual readers' accounts or personally
identifiable information.
Personally identifiable information:
We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties, with one limited
exception: we may disclose personally identifiable information about you if we have a
good faith belief that doing so is required by law, such as pursuant to a subpoena or other
judicial or administrative order.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping
purposes. We use cookies on this site. The information we store in cookies is, in some
cases, linked to readers' accounts.
We use both short-term cookies and persistent cookies. A short-term cookie expires
within a limited period of time. We use session cookies so that readers with accounts can
navigate and contribute to our site without logging in multiple times over a short period
of time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.
We use persistent cookies to recognize account holders and present the site accordingly.
You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's
"help" file.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our
site, such as comments, will require logging in for each action you want to take.
Third-party Advertisers
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to readers by Federated Media, our
advertising partner. Federated Media, and companies it contracts with to serve some ads,
may place or recognize unique cookies on your browser and use information about your
visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other
sites about goods and services. The information collected does not include personally
identifiable information like your name, address, email address or telephone number. It
does include IP addresses, though these are not tied to individual readers' accounts. If you
would like more information about Federated Media's practices, contact
authorservices@federatedmedia.net .
Links to Other Sites
This Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by
krebsonsecurity.com. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy
practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected
by this Web site.
Changes in This Privacy Statement
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy
statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of
what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we
disclose it.
